[
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "Cross the T's",
    "back": "Be meticulous",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "formality"
    ],
    "id": 0
  },
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "Pretty good",
    "back": "Be meticulous",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "formality"
    ],
    "id": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "face the music",
    "back": "acept the concequence",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "formality"
    ],
    "id": 2
  },
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "under de water",
    "back": "In a bad situation",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "formality"
    ],
    "id": 3
  },
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "control the room",
    "back": "Take control of your feelings",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "formality"
    ],
    "id": 4
  },
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "have the way in words",
    "back": "have the way in words",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "formality"
    ],
    "id": 5
  },
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "talking the same language",
    "back": "have the way in words",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "formality"
    ],
    "id": 6
  },
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "talking the same language",
    "back": "have the way in words",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "formality"
    ],
    "id": 7
  },
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "we must have reduced the issues, if we were..",
    "back": "have the way in words",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "formality"
    ],
    "id": 8
  },
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "we must have reduced the issues, if we were..",
    "back": "have the way in words",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "formality"
    ],
    "id": 9
  },
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "like father, like son",
    "back": "Sons often are similar to their parents",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "formality"
    ],
    "id": 10
  },
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "Then again",
    "back": "Contradictory",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "formality"
    ],
    "id": 11
  },
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "straigh the horses mouth",
    "back": "Contradictory",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "formality"
    ],
    "id": 12
  },
  {
    "type": "idiom",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "Acid test",
    "back": "Proves the effectiveness of something",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      ""
    ],
    "id": 13
  },
  {
    "type": "grammar",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "For + -ing",
    "back": "Used to express purpose",
    "example": "This tool is for cutting.",
    "tags": [
      "prepositions",
      "verbs"
    ],
    "id": 14
  },
  {
    "type": "grammar",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "Not only .... But also",
    "back": "Used to express purpose",
    "example": "This tool is for cutting.",
    "tags": [
      "prepositions",
      "verbs"
    ],
    "id": 15
  },
  {
    "type": "grammar",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "I am amazed at how",
    "back": "Used to express admiration",
    "example": "This tool is for cutting.",
    "tags": [
      "prepositions",
      "verbs"
    ],
    "id": 16
  },
  {
    "type": "grammar",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "I hope to",
    "back": "Esperar algo",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "prepositions",
      "verbs"
    ],
    "id": 17
  },
  {
    "type": "grammar",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "In doing so",
    "back": "Al hacerlo",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "prepositions",
      "verbs"
    ],
    "id": 18
  },
  {
    "type": "grammar",
    "language": "English",
    "front": "bury the hatche",
    "back": "Al hacerlo",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [
      "prepositions",
      "verbs"
    ],
    "id": 19
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "in favor of",
    "back": "a favor de",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 20
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "tirelessly",
    "back": "incansablemente",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 21
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "Rashly",
    "back": "precipitadamente",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 22
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "in a manner that is hasty",
    "back": "de manera apresurada",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 23
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "carry out",
    "back": "Llevar a cabo",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 24
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "properly",
    "back": "propiamente",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 25
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "in the know",
    "back": "en la juega",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 26
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "cutting down",
    "back": "Reducir",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 27
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "how long",
    "back": "cuanto tiempo",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 28
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "how it does it is not a concern",
    "back": "como lo hace, no es una preocupacion",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 29
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "but you have to sit absolutely still",
    "back": "pero tienes que sentarte absolutamente quieto",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 30
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "I'm telling yoo",
    "back": "te lo digo",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 31
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "far before",
    "back": "Mucho antes",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 32
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "even I would rather be watching",
    "back": "incluso yo preferiria estar viendo ...",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 33
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "nowhere near that",
    "back": "Ni de serca",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 34
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "when do we get to see the sun",
    "back": "cuando podremos ver el sol",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 35
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "by default",
    "back": "por defecto",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 36
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "in the know",
    "back": "sabidos",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 37
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "past + would",
    "back": "ia ej: presumia, acogia, hacia",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 38
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "If needed, Alex would allocate additional resources",
    "back": "Si fuera necesario, alex asignaria recursos ...",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 39
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "yellow-bellied",
    "back": "coward",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 40
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "Works like a charm",
    "back": "Works very well or as expected",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 41
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "if needed",
    "back": "Si es necesario",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 42
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "Throw one self into",
    "back": "lanzarse contra",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 43
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "roadblock",
    "back": "obstaculo",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 44
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "hindrance",
    "back": "obstaculo",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 45
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "though",
    "back": "Aunque con",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 46
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "sharp eye",
    "back": "ojo agudo",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 47
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "tenfold",
    "back": "diez veces",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 48
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "Do + verb infinitive",
    "back": "recomendacion",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 49
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Mixed",
    "front": "Do make sure you chosse the correct time to say that",
    "back": "asegurate de elegir el tiempo correcto para decirlo",
    "example": "",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 50
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Spanish-English",
    "front": "rechazar",
    "back": "turn down",
    "example": "I'll have to turn down the invitation",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 51
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Spanish-English",
    "front": "por",
    "back": "Because of",
    "example": "Because of the wheter",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 52
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Spanish-English",
    "front": "urgente",
    "back": "Pressing",
    "example": "Because of a pressing issue",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 53
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Spanish-English",
    "front": "repasar",
    "back": "brush up",
    "example": "I scheduled a meeting with you to go over lifting",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 54
  },
  {
    "type": "vocabulary",
    "language": "Spanish-English",
    "front": "hacer seguimiento",
    "back": "keep track",
    "example": "I am not able to keep track of all our emails",
    "tags": [],
    "id": 55
  }
]